<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting started on Political Science Research Methods</title>
    <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting started on Political Science Research Methods</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Fanghui Zhao 2019 &lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-tree&#34; style=&#34;color: #40a990;&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/search/</guid>
      <description>Empower your users to search your website content for keywords so that they can quickly discover relevant content.
If search is enabled, a search icon will automatically appear in the navigation bar and a search box will appear in the sidebar of any content using the docs/tutorial layout (as can be seen on this site). Clicking the search icon will toggle the search dialog.
Keyboard shortcuts are available to facilitate searching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain Name</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/domain/</guid>
      <description>If you choose a deployment option such as Netlify or Github pages, you will be automatically assigned a free URL for your website. You can further personalize your website with your own domain name.
We can highly recommend Namecheap for registering a domain, as they provide great value for money whilst providing fast support. To find a good domain that is available, try a mix of your first and last names or initials, with either a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Sites built using Academic can be deployed in a large variety of ways due to the static nature of the generated website. The recommended deployment method alongside a few of the other most popular techniques are described below.
If using Netlify, your site will be built automatically, otherwise run the hugo command in your terminal to generate your site in the public/ folder - now it is ready to copy across to your host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Wordpress</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/migrate-from-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/migrate-from-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>To migrate your website from Wordpress to Academic is a two phase process:
Phase One First, install the WordPress to Jekyll Exporter plugin into your Wordpress installation by following these steps:
 Place the WordPress to Jekyll Exporter plugin in /wp-content/plugins/ folder Activate plugin in WordPress dashboard Select Export to Jekyll from the Tools menu  The WordPress plugin converts all posts, pages, taxonomies, metadata, and settings to Markdown and YAML with just a single click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Matter</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/front-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/front-matter/</guid>
      <description>Front matter allows page-specific variables to be included at the top of a Markdown file using TOML format, set between triple-plus +++ lines. The variables may include metadata such as page title, date published, author, categories, tags, and so on. Here is a simple example:
+++ date = 2017-12-01 title = &amp;quot;My first blog post&amp;quot; +++  Each configuration section (referred to as a table in TOML) is defined by a name in square brackets (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customization</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/customization/</guid>
      <description>It is possible to carry out many customizations without editing any code in the themes/academic/ folder, making it easier to update the framework in the future.
Custom theme To customize the color theme, you can copy a theme such as themes/academic/data/themes/default.toml to data/themes/default.toml (at the root of your site, not in themes/academic/), creating the data/themes/ folders if they do not already exist. Now you can adjust the colors within your theme file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback &amp; Contributing</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Please use the issue tracker to report bugs or submit feature requests. Alternatively, feel free to modify the code and submit a pull request on Github.
For general questions about Hugo, there is a Hugo discussion forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/get-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/get-started/</guid>
      <description>This quick tutorial will show you how to setup and use Academic.
Choose the right theme for you Check out the available color themes and have fun choosing a design you love.
Once you have settled on a theme, edit your config.toml file in a text editor and set the color_theme option to the name of the chosen theme.
The following font styles are also available and can be set by the font option in config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/install/</guid>
      <description>You can choose from one of the following four methods to install:
 one-click install using your web browser (recommended) install on your computer using Git with the Command Prompt/Terminal app install on your computer by downloading the ZIP files install on your computer with RStudio  Hugo v0.49+ is required if installing on your computer.
Install with web browser  Install Academic with Netlify  Netlify will provide you with a customizable URL to access your new site  On GitHub, go to your newly created academic-kickstart repository and edit config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language and translation</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/language/</guid>
      <description>Both the interface and content language can be changed to suit your needs.
Interface The Interface Language is used to change the language throughout your site. The following interface languages are currently available: English, 中文 (简体), Español, Português, Deutsch, Euskara, Français, Italiano, 日本語, 한국어, Nederlands, Polski, Русский, Türkçe, Tiếng Việt and Catalan.
The interface text is stored in language files which are collected from Academic&amp;rsquo;s themes/academic/i18n/ folder, as well as an i18n/ folder at the root of your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Widgets</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/widgets/</guid>
      <description>Widgets empower you to fully customize your site. They display as sections on the homepage or on widget pages. They can be enabled/disabled and configured as desired. Academic has the following widgets available to use:
 About/biography Featured publications Recent publications Recent news/blog posts Projects Featured talks Recent talks Contact Tag cloud Hero (call-to-action) Featurette (showcase key features or skills) Search Carousel Custom widget (add your own content!)  The example site that you copied to create your site uses all the different types of widget (except talks), so you can generally just delete the widgets you don&amp;rsquo;t need and customize the parameters of the widgets you wish to keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing content</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/managing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/managing-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a brief guide to managing content with the Academic framework. Content can include publications, projects, talks, news/blog articles, and widget pages. After you have read this guide about creating and managing content, you may also be interested to learn about &lt;a href=&#34;https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/writing-markdown-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/writing-markdown-latex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content can be written using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/adam-p/markdown-here/wiki/Markdown-Cheatsheet&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikibooks.org/wiki/LaTeX/Mathematics&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LaTeX math&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/extras/shortcodes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, HTML may be used for advanced formatting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/faq/</guid>
      <description>Common questions and answers will be listed here.
I cloned/downloaded Academic but Hugo produces errors when using it with my existing Hugo site
Academic is a website framework rather than just a theme. Therefore, you must follow the full installation guide found on the Demo/Documentation website or in the Github Readme. If you still have problems, first try running Hugo on the Academic Example Site found in the themes/academic/exampleSite folder and then compare the configuration parameters in the Example Site&amp;rsquo;s config.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fanghuiz.github.io/docs/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few tips for migrating an existing website from Jekyll to Hugo. These tips can be applied in conjunction with following Hugo Academic&amp;rsquo;s getting started guide.
Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>